Harvard University, Graduate School of Design. The GSD History Collection, Administrative Affairs: An Inventory
Harvard University, Graduate School of Design. The GSD History Collection, Administrative Affairs: An Inventory
- Series F: Harvard University GSD, Administrative Affairs: Miscellaneous and Photographs, / Date(s): 1940-2001 (inclusive) -- 1940-1963 (bulk); F000; / Quantity: 3 boxes; 1 oversize folder / Dimensions: 4 linear ft. / Medium: varies / Support: varies
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1996-1997; Folder: FA024; / Quantity: 17 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Packet of information materials distributed to students for the 1996-1997 academic year. Includes "Orientation and Registration Schedule" "Cross-Registration Procedures", and "Draft Courses of Instruction in the Faculty of Design."
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1996-1997; Folder: FA025; / Quantity: 1 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: GSD Course Bulletin, Fall 1996.
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1996-1997; Folder: FA026; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Playing it Safe, Harvard University Safety and Security Guide, 1996 Annual Campus Crime and Security Report.
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1996-1997; Folder: FA027; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Official Register, Harvard University Graduate School of Design, 1996-1997.
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1996; Folder: FA028; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 16" x 11-1/2" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Issue of Harvard University Gazette (Commencement 1996 issue).
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1996; Folder: FA029; / Quantity: 5 items / Dimensions: varies / Medium: newsprint / Support: paper
    Note: Several obituaries of Serge Chermayeff, 1900-1996 (head of the Architecture Department at GSD, 1953-1962). Also includes obituary of Frances Lehman Loeb (1906-1996).
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1996; Folder: FA030; / Quantity: 9 items / Dimensions: 11" x 8-1/2"; 10" x 6"; 6" x 4-1/2" / Medium: newsprint / Support: paper
    Note: Several leaflets, brochures and program related to 1996 Commencement festivities.
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1996; Folder: FA031; / Quantity: 13 items / Dimensions: 11" x 8-1/2"; 11-1/2" x 6"; 8-1/2" x 7" / Medium: newsprint / Support: paper
    Note: Miscellaneous materials related to events (lectures and exhibitions) during the 1996-1997 academic year: "Exploring the Landscape Architecture of Richard Haag"; "Boston's New Urban Ring: An Antidote to Fragmentation". Also includes clipping on Moneo's winning the Pritzker Prize, and the Mayor's Institute on City Design, held at the GSD and sponsored by the NEA and GSD.
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1990-1995; Folder: FA032; / Quantity: 3 items / Dimensions: 11" x 8-1/2" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: GSD Academic Calendar 1994-1995 and A Guide to Harvard University Library, 1990.
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1993-1994; Folder: FA033; / Quantity: 3 items / Dimensions: 11" x 8-1/2" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Lefalets: GSD Academic Calendar, 1993-1994, and GSD Events, Spring 1994.
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1996; Folder: FA034; / Quantity: 5 items / Dimensions: 11" x 8-1/2"; 5-1/2" x 8-1/2"; 4-1/2" x 6" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: File includes miscellaneous leaflets, brochures, and invitation cards: "Seeing the Past as Part of our Future" (from Gas Works Park, Seattle); "Deep Into the City: A Photographic Exploration of Toronto Ravines" (by Steven Evans); "Richard Haag: A Selected Bibliography"; "Invitation to a Dinner in Honor of Jorge Francisco Liernur, architectural historian, Buenos Aires."
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1996; Folder: FA035; / Quantity: 2 items / Dimensions: 22" x 16" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Two identical posters for: The New Inside The New: Latin American Architecture and Urbanism, and the Crisis of the International Style, 1937-1954, held at the GSD, 1996 (in collaboration with the David Rockefeller Center for Latin American Studies).
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1996; Folder: FA036; / Quantity: 5 items / Dimensions: 11" x 8-1/2" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Appointment announcements for Wade Hokoda (Director of Computer Resources) and George Hargreaves (Chairman of the Department of Landscape Architecture). Both appointments done by Dean Peter Rowe, 1996. Also includes announcement of the 1996 Veronica Rudge Prize in Urban Design awarded to the City of Mexico for its restoration of the historic center of Mexico City (1988-1994).
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1996; Folder: FA037; / Quantity: 11 items / Dimensions: 8" x 8"; 4-1/2" x 7" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Brochures and cards related to events at GSD, 1995-1996: "The Michael Sorkin Studio: Urbanagrams"; "Patkau Architects: Selected Projects, 1983-1994"; "Tokyo International Forum: Rafael Vinoly Architects"; and "1996 Veronica Rudge Green Prize in Architecture."
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1995-1996; Folder: FA038; / Quantity: 11 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11"; 4-1/2" x 6" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Miscellaneous leaflets related to GSD staff events, and a couple of bibliographies prepared for the public lecture series, 1995-1996.
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1995-1996; Folder: FA039; / Quantity: 2 items / Dimensions: 22" x 16" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Poster for exhibitions and lectures at GSD, Spring 1996; and poster for symposium held at GSD: Manufacturing Cities: Competitive Advantage and the Urban Industrial Community, 1996.
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1995-1996; Folder: FA040; / Quantity: 9 items / Dimensions: 11" x 8-1/2"; 6-1/2" x 6" / Medium: print; printouts / Support: paper
    Note: File includes miscellaneous brochures about events at GSD: "Open House for Prospective Students"; "Questions of Scale: Research on Three OMA Buildings"; "Professional Development at GSD"; and "Design Asia Lunch-Bag Series" held by Asia GSD. Bibliographies included were produced fior the public lecture series and include: selected bibliographies of Michael Sorkin and Eric Owen Moss. Included as well is the bibliography for "Library Planning and Technology", and for a Fine Arts Seminar "Reading in Public" by Randy Bird and Michael Samra.
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1995-1996; Folder: FA041; / Quantity: 9 items / Dimensions: 8" x 8"; 9" x 4"; 18" x 28" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Posters and brochures of exhibitions and lectures at GSD, as well as a couple of brochures for the Loeb Fellowship Program and the Community Service Program at GSD. Includes "Off-the-Shelf: The Landscapes of Martha Schwartz."
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1995-1996; Folder: FA042; / Quantity: 13 items / Dimensions: 11" x 8-1/2" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Miscellaneous leaflets related to GSD staff topics as well as appointment announcements. Also includes list of books to be pulled out of the Rare Book Room for Mirka Benes' class.
    Note: Also included is Loeb Fellowship Forum on occassion of the 25th anniversary of the Loeb Fellowship.
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1994-1995; Folder: FA043; / Quantity: 22 items / Dimensions: 11" x 8-1/2" / Medium: print; printouts / Support: paper
    Note: Numerous notes, flyers and memorandums related to events and appointments at GSD, academic year 1994-1995. Includes a Mack Scogin bibliography.
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1995; Folder: FA044; / Quantity: 8 items / Dimensions: 8" x 8" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Brochures for exhibitions held at GSD in 1995. Includes Portrait of the Body: Work by Chris Risher, Jr. and In Real Life (GSD Staff Art Exhibition). Also includes invitation cards for lectures and events.
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1995; Folder: FA045; / Quantity: 12 items / Dimensions: 11" x 8-1/2"; 8" x 8" / Medium: print; printouts / Support: paper
    Note: Leaflets, memos, and brochures of events, appointments and exhibitions at GSD. Includes brochure for Landscape Architecture Drawings from the Historic American Building Survey and the Historic American Engineering Record held at the GSD, 1995. Also includes copy of Loeb Fellowship Forum (Fall 1994), and GSD Design Lines (GSD staff newsletter); and a bibliography of Fran Lebowitz. Materials for farewell event for Martha Mahard included.
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1995; Folder: FA046; / Quantity: 2 items / Dimensions: 8" x 8"; 15" x 11" / Medium: print; printouts / Support: paper
    Note: Brochures for exhibition Stairs and Ramps from the Architecture of Jose Antonio Martinez Lapena and Elias Torres; and pamphlet for Professional Development Courses, Summer 1995.
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1995; Folder: FA047; / Quantity: 3 items / Dimensions: 17" x 12" / Medium: newsprint / Support: paper
    Note: Three issues of Harvard University Gazette, one with headline "Loebs Make Record Gift to University."
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1995; Folder: FA048; / Quantity: 17 items / Dimensions: 11" x 8-1/2"; 17" x 12"; 4-1/2" x 5-1/2" / Medium: print; newsprint; printouts / Support: paper
    Note: Leaflets, memos, and brochures of events, appointments and exhibitions at GSD, 1995. Includes "Elias Torres: A Selected Bibliography." Includes clipping from Harvard University Gazette: "Architect of Ideas: Jorge Silvetti takes a Broad, and Optimistic, Approach to Architecture" and bibliographies related to Elias Torres and to Diana Balmori.
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1995; Folder: FA049; / Quantity: 17 items / Dimensions: 8" x 8"; 18" x 28" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Brochures and posters for exhibitons and events at GSD, 1995. Includes An Architecture for All Senses: The Work of Eileen Gray; and Delineating the Edge: Mapping the Boston and New England Coasts.
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1994; Folder: FA050; / Quantity: 12 items / Dimensions: 11" x 8-1/2" / Medium: print; printouts / Support: paper
    Note: File includes bibliographies on Elizabeth Diller, Cesar Pelli, and Antonio Ortiz. Also includes a number of Loeb Fellowship Forum (Vol. 1 No. 1), GSD Design Lines, and Staff Connection.
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1994; Folder: FA051; / Quantity: 7 items / Dimensions: 11" x 8-1/2" / Medium: printouts / Support: paper
    Note: Charles Gwathmey bibliography, and miscellaneous newsletters and staff communications. Includes GSD Staff Newsletter.
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1994; Folder: FA052; / Quantity: 2 items / Dimensions: 4-1/2" x 6"; 8-1/2" x 5-1/2" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Invitation card and brochure for In Real Life, and exhibit of art by the staff of the GSD.
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1994; Folder: FA053; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 15" x 11" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Pamphlet Professional Development Courses Summer 1994.
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1993-1994; Folder: FA054; / Quantity: 40 items / Dimensions: 11" x 8-1/2" / Medium: printouts / Support: paper
    Note: Bibliographies for the GSD Lecture Series for the academic year 1993-1994. Includes bibliographies for Bernard Tschumi, Therese O'Malley, Michel Corajoud, Jacques Herzog, Jean Nouvel, Ignasi Sola Morales, Luigi Snozzi, Edmund Happold. Also includes "Reference Sources for Landscape Architecture."
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1991; Folder: FA055; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 11" x 11" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: GSD News, Fall 1991.
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1996-1997; Folder: FA056; / Quantity: 24 items / Dimensions: 11" x 8-1/2" / Medium: print; printouts; newsprint / Support: paper
    Note: Miscellaneous flyers, brochures and notices related to events at GSD, 1996-1997 academic year. Includes brochures with schedule and program for Commencement 1997.
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1997; Folder: FA057; / Quantity: 11 items / Dimensions: 8" x 8"; 8" x 6-1/2"; 4" x 9" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Brochures and flyers for exhibitions and events at GSD, 1997. Included are: Asian Urbanization: Transformation + Continuity (organized by Asia GSD; Projecting Beirut (conference), Reflections: Watercolors by Lauretta Vinciarelli; Juan Navarro Baldeweg: Complimentary Geometry; and Buildings in the City: Work of Enrique Norten.
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1997; Folder: FA058; / Quantity: 2 items / Dimensions: 24" x 18"; 18" x 11" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Two brochures / posters for lectures and exhibitions held at, or sponsored by, GSD, 1997.
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1997; Folder: FA059; / Quantity: 2 items / Dimensions: 16" x 11" / Medium: newsprint / Support: paper
    Note: Clippings about George Hargreaves, includes Harvard University's Gazette with article "Landscape Alchemist: GSD's George Hargreaves Transforms Post-Industrial Wastelands Into Aesthetic and Functional Spaces."
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1997; Folder: FA060; / Quantity: 32 items / Dimensions: 11" x 8-1/2" / Medium: print; printouts / Support: paper
    Note: Miscellaneous flyers, notes and newsletters about events and everyday business at GSD. Includes the following bibliographies for public lectures series: "Craig Hodgetts and Ming Fu" and "Juan Navarro Baldeweg."
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1996-1997; Folder: FA061; / Quantity: 2 items / Dimensions: 11" x 8-1/2" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: File includes GSD Course Bulletin for the Fall 1996, and Spring 1997.
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1996; Folder: FA062; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 11-1/2" x 5" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: GSD Telephone Directory, Fall 1996.
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1996; Folder: FA063; / Quantity: 20 items / Dimensions: 11" x 8-1/2" / Medium: print; printouts; newsprint / Support: paper
    Note: Miscellaneous flyers, notes and newsletters about events and everyday business at GSD. Includes the following bibliography for public lectures series: "Morris Lapidus." Includes obituary from the Harvard Gazette for long-time GSD benefactor and patron John Langeloth Loeb.
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1996; Folder: FA064; / Quantity: 9 items / Dimensions: 11" x 8-1/2" / Medium: print; printouts / Support: paper
    Note: Notes, flyers, and newsletters related to events at GSD and university-wide. Includes bibliography for Tod Williams and Billie Tsien.
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1994-1995; Folder: FA065; / Quantity: 3 items / Dimensions: 8" x 8" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Brochures for the following exhibitions held at GSD: An Architecture for All Senses: The Work of Eileen Gray; Making a Landscape of Continuity: The Practice of Innocenti and Webel; and Envisioning Design: Special Collections.
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1996-1997; Folder: FA066; / Quantity: 2 items / Dimensions: 7" x 7"; 9" x 4" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: Brochures for the Carpenter Center and for the Department of Visual and Environmental Studies: Visiting Faculty and Guest Lecturers 1996/9.
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1996-1997; Folder: FA067; / Quantity: 36 items / Dimensions: 11" x 8-1/2"; 8-1/2" x 5-1/2" / Medium: print; printouts / Support: paper
    Note: Miscellaneous fliers, memorandums, and booklets related to activities, courses and/or events at GSD. Includes booklets for "Harvard Recreation" and "Staff Art" (In Real Life).
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): n.d.; Folder: FA068; / Quantity: 36 items / Dimensions: 11" x 8-1/2" / Medium: copies / Support: paper
    Note: Copies of what appear to be reference files for (including articles by) architectural firms and/or individual architects. This folder includes: Archizoom, Denise Scott Brown, Aldo Rossi, Peter Eisenman.
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): n.d.; Folder: FA069; / Quantity: 23 items / Dimensions: 11" x 8-1/2" / Medium: copies / Support: paper
    Note: Copies of what appear to be reference files for (including articles by) architectural institutions, firms and/or individual architects. This folder includes: Beaux Arts Forum Institute, Robert Venturi, Charles Jencks, Rem Koolhaas, James Stirling, Michael Graves, Leon Krier.
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): n.d.; Folder: FA070; / Quantity: 27 items / Dimensions: 11" x 8-1/2" / Medium: copies / Support: paper
    Note: Copies of what appear to be reference files for (including articles by) architectural firms and/or individual architects. This folder includes: Frank Gehry, Coop Himmelblau, Daniel Libeskind.
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1986-1987; Folder: FA071; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 11" x 5-1/2" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: GSD Students, 1986-1987. Booklet with names and photographs of students for that academic year.
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1994-1996; Folder: FA072; / Quantity: 2 items / Dimensions: 11" x 5-1/2" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: GSD Student Facebook, 1994-1995 and 1995-1996. Booklet with names and photographs of students for those academic years.
  - Subseries FA: GSD Miscellaneous, / Date(s): 1996-1998; Folder: FA073; / Quantity: 2 items / Dimensions: 11" x 5-1/2" / Medium: print / Support: paper
    Note: GSD Student Facebook, 1996-1997 and 1997-1998. Booklet with names and photographs of students for those academic years.
  - Subseries FB: GSD Photographs, / Date(s): 1940-2000 (inclusive) -- 1953-1963 (bulk); Subseries: FB000; / Quantity: 97 folders / Dimensions: 2 linear ft. / Medium: print; typescript / Support: paper
    Note: Subseries FB: GSD Photographs is comprised of 97 folders (GSD History - Administrative. Boxes 22 and 23) and contains photographs of GSD life, including events, lectures, exhibitions, faculty, and students.
  - Subseries FB: GSD Photographs, / Date(s): 1949-1950; Folder: FB001; / Quantity: 14 / Dimensions: 11" x 8-1/2" / Medium: black-and-white photographs / Support: photographic paper
    Note: Xerographic copies of photographs of students with Gropius.
  - Subseries FB: GSD Photographs, / Date(s): 1945-1946; Folder: FB002; / Quantity: 7 items / Dimensions: 6-1/2" x 9-1/2" / Medium: black-and-white photographs / Support: photographic paper
    Note: Photographs of student work (Harry Seidler) for Walter Gropius' master class, 1946. Includes portrait of Seidler outside of Robinson Hall, 1945.
  - Subseries FB: GSD Photographs, / Date(s): 1994; Folder: FB003; / Quantity: 13 items / Dimensions: 3-1/2" x 5" / Medium: black-and-white photographs / Support: photographic paper
    Note: Photographs of Dean Peter Rowe in a cocktail reception in China (includes note from alumni). Among attendants some alumni. Another photograph shows Peter Rowe, Ada de Bass and Oscar Grauer at an event probably in Latin America (Venezuela)
  - Subseries FB: GSD Photographs, / Date(s): 2000-2001; Folder: FB004; / Quantity: 2 items / Dimensions: 8-1/2" x 11"; 8-1/2" x 5-1/2" / Medium: ink / Support: paper
    Note: Two notes, one from Gerald Holton, the other James Herold, about photographs being sent to GSD (photographs are not included).
  - Subseries FB: GSD Photographs, / Date(s): early 1940s; Folder: FB005; / Quantity: 16 items / Dimensions: 3-1/2" x 5" / Medium: black-and-white photographs / Support: photographic paper
    Note: Photographs of party at Robinson Hall, people in costume. Included among those photographed are Walter Gropius, Joseph Hudnut, Hugh Stubbins, Laurence Halprin, Anne Tyng, Marcel Breuer and Eileen Pei.
  - Subseries FB: GSD Photographs, / Date(s): early 1940s; Folder: FB006; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 8" x 10" / Medium: black-and-white photographs / Support: photographic paper; (mounted) foamcore
    Note: Photograph of party (event) at Robinson Hall with Gropius being handed a bottle of champagne by Anna Halprin. People in costume.
  - Subseries FB: GSD Photographs, / Date(s): early 1940s; Folder: FB007; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 8" x 10" / Medium: black-and-white photographs / Support: photographic paper; (mounted) foamcore
    Note: Photograph of party (event) at Robinson Hall with people in costume dancing; at center Lawrence and Anna Halprin.
  - Subseries FB: GSD Photographs, / Date(s): 1986; Folder: FB008; / Quantity: 13 items / Dimensions: 8" x 10" / Medium: black-and-white photographs / Support: photographic paper
    Note: Photographs of Harvard's 350th Anniversary, as well as GSD 50th Anniversary. Photographs include Dean Gerald McCue, President Derek Bok, and Prince Charles at Harvard Convocation. Other shots show celebration cake (in the form of Gund Hall), the Harvard Yard, Tercentenary Theater, and Piper Auditorium. Also includes Harvard Stadium celebration. Photographers are credited on the verso of the photographs.
  - Subseries FB: GSD Photographs, / Date(s): 1986; Folder: FB009; / Quantity: 8 items / Dimensions: 8" x 10" / Medium: black-and-white photographs / Support: photographic paper
    Note: Photograph of the GSD's 50th Anniversary. Banquet with tables on trays of Gund Hall. Cake with depiction of Robinson Hall. Among attendees Edward Larrabee Barnes, Joseph Wasserman, and Rafael Moneo.
  - Subseries FB: GSD Photographs, / Date(s): ca. 1905; Folder: FB010; / Quantity: 8 items / Dimensions: 8" x 10"; 5" x 7" / Medium: black-and-white photographs / Support: photographic paper
    Note: Two photographs (interior and exterior) of Robinson Hall, ca. 1905
  - Subseries FB: GSD Photographs, / Date(s): 1986; Folder: FB011; / Quantity: 5 items / Dimensions: 8" x 10" / Medium: black-and-white photographs / Support: photographic paper
    Note: Photographs taken at Gund Hall, showing exhibition held for the 50th Anniversary of the GSD.
  - Subseries FB: GSD Photographs, / Date(s): 1961; Folder: FB012; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 8" x 10" / Medium: contacts / Support: photographic paper
    Note: Contact sheet of Urban Design Conference, speaker: Giedion on "Constancy and Change in Architecture", 15 April 1961.
  - Subseries FB: GSD Photographs, / Date(s): 1996; Folder: FB013; / Quantity: 11 item / Dimensions: 8" x 10" / Medium: contacts; black-and-white photographs / Support: photographic paper
    Note: Photographs of Green Prize in 1996 (awarded to the City of Mexico). Dean Peter Rowe in many photographs.
  - Subseries FB: GSD Photographs, / Date(s): 1994; Folder: FB014; / Quantity: 16 item / Dimensions: 6" x 4"; 2" x 2"; 5" x 7"; 8" x 10" / Medium: black-and-white photographs; slides / Support: photographic paper
    Note: Photographs from the files of GSD News. Mainly portraits, including Mack Scogin, Dan Kiley, Doris Cole, Merrill Elam, Mehrdad Yazdani.
  - Subseries FB: GSD Photographs, / Date(s): n.d.; Folder: FB015; / Quantity: 1 item / Dimensions: 8" x 10" / Medium: black-and-white photographs; slides / Support: photographic paper
    Note: Photograph of student work, n.d. Includes Ref. Gg 22 abc.